nationalmerit.org 2011-09-26

# National Merit Scholarship Corporation - Competition Steps

National Merit Scholarship Corporation ("NMSC") shares your concerns for maintaining the integrity and privacy of personal information collected on the Internet. The following Privacy Policy is intended to explain our information collection and dissemination practices in connection with the websites ("Sites") owned and operated by NMSC. 

### Collection of Personal Information from Site Users

While visiting our Sites, you may choose to provide personal information to NMSC. This information may include, but is not limited to, your name, date of birth, e-mail address, postal address, telephone number, and your parents' names and employment information. By providing your personal information, you consent to allow NMSC to use that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

### Compliance with the Federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA)

NMSC is committed to helping participating schools to comply with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974. In accordance with FERPA, before a school may release student records to NMSC, it is required that a parent or legal guardian consent to such release. 

### Collection of Personal Information from Children

The Sites and NMSC's programs are not directed at individuals under thirteen years of age ("Child") and NMSC will not knowingly (1) collect information from a Child or (2) disclose any information relating to a Child, for any purpose whatsoever. 

### Security Measures

NMSC has implemented numerous security features to prevent the unauthorized release of or access to personal information, including use of a secure server to encrypt personal information provided to NMSC. Please note that, while NMSC has endeavored to create secure and reliable Sites, the security and confidentiality of any communication transmitted to or from NMSC via the Sites or the Internet cannot be 100% guaranteed. Accordingly, NMSC is not responsible for the security and confidentiality of information transmitted via the Internet. 

### Use and Disclosure of Personal Information Collected 

NMSC uses third-party vendors to host the Sites and provide other services. By submitting your personal information, you authorize NMSC and its third-party vendors to obtain and use your personal information solely for the purpose of endeavoring to provide and providing scholarships to the applicants and any renewals thereof (including, releasing such information to corporations, company foundations, colleges and universities, and other entities and individuals); to verify the information you have provided; to insure the integrity of NMSC's processes; to communicate with you about scholarships and other NMSC services; and to otherwise offer services provided by NMSC. NMSC may also aggregate personal information it receives through the Sites for research and statistical purposes. NMSC does not use your personal information for marketing or promotional purposes, except to the extent expressly stated in this Privacy Policy. Moreover, NMSC does not sell personal information received through its Sites. 

###  Inquiries and Concerns 

The foregoing Privacy Policy is effective as of January, 2010. NMSC may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. All amended terms automatically take effect when they are posted on the Sites. You agree to periodically review the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Sites, following reasonable notice of any changes, will be conclusively deemed acceptance of such changes. You agree that notice of changes to the Privacy Policy posted on the Sites, delivered by email, or provided in any other reasonable way, constitutes reasonable and sufficient notice. 

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at: 

Telephone: (847) 866-5100 

|  Mailing Address:  |  **National Merit Scholarship Corporation**  
---|---  
  |  1560 Sherman Avenue   
  |  Suite 200   
  |  Evanston, Illinois 60201-4897   
  
### Terms of Use

Please also visit the Terms of Use found at <http://www.nationalmerit.org/terms>, incorporated here by reference, that explain other important terms governing your use of NMSC's Sites.
